嘿 伙计们
Hey, guys.
外面冷的要死 你的外套呢?
It's freezing out\nthere. Where's your coat?
Ted 我是加拿大人 用不着穿外套
Ted, I'm Canadian. I don't need a coat.
这天气对我来说简直是小儿科
This kind of weather is nothing for me.
是啊 要不是大街上的出租和\n满眼的摩天大楼以及黄棕黑非白色人种
Yeah. This is like a spring\nday back in Minnesota,
这简直就像明尼苏达州\n春暖花开的日子
if it weren't for all the taxis and\nthe skyscrapers and non-white people.
明尼苏达没黑人的么?
There aren't any black\npeople in Minnesota?
Prince巡演去了就没了\n(Prince--美国黑人音乐家)
Not if Prince is on tour.
老爸老妈浪漫史\n第四季 第11集
How I Met Your\nMother Season04 Episode11
我妹妹的飞机一小时前已经降落了\n用气象学家的话来说
Well, my sister's plane got in an hour\nago, or as a meteorologist might say,
Heather飓风刚刚登陆
Hurricane Heather has\njust made landfall.
别这样 她也没那么差劲吧
Come on. She's not that bad.
咱来看看她都有哪些"案底"
Here's the back of\nHeather's baseball card.
她花了6年时间从3所不同的大学里毕业
It took her six years to graduate\nfrom three different colleges,
在此期间 撞坏了2辆车 \n做了5天人家的老婆
during which time she wrecked two\ncars, got married for five days,
在树上住了9个礼拜 最后才弄明白\n其实没人想砍那棵树
and lived in a tree for nine weeks, only to realize\nthat no one had any intention of cutting it down.
而现在 Heather说她要搬到纽约来
And now, Heather says\nshe's moving to New York.
哇 大新闻诶
Wow, that's big news.
她不会撑多久的
She's never gonna go through with it.
记得几年前她说要\n转到纽约大学那事吗?
Remember a few years back when she\ntalked about transferring to NYU?
就在入学面试当天...
And then, on the day of\nthe admissions interview...
Heather? 我沙发跟电视上哪儿去了?
Heather? Where's my couch and my TV?
我卖了 买了Nine Inch Nails演唱会门票\n(Nine Inch Nails--重金属乐队)
I sold them for Nine Inch Nails tickets.
光电视就值2000块诶
The TV alone is worth two grand.
最后一分钟才买的机票很贵的嘛
Well, a last-minute\nplane ticket is expensive.
等等 你在哪儿?
Wait. Where are you?
西班牙的某个圪
Somewhere in Spain.
我挂了 到慢歌了
Gotta go. Slow song.
哦 见鬼 是Barney
Oh, crap. It's Barney.
那又怎么了?
So?
这些年来Heather来过纽约好多次\nTed都绝不让Barney见她
For all the years Heather's been visiting\nNew York, Ted's never let Barney meet her.
以后也不会
And I never will.
每年圣诞节 \n只要看到Mosby家的贺卡...
Every year when the Mosby\nfamily Christmas card shows up...
拽下她的小热裤
Pulling down her pants
扯掉我的短裤头
Yanking off my own
相约圣诞树下
Underneath the mistletoe
让你妹妹爽歪歪
I'll make your sister moan
Heather真性感 Heather真热辣
Heather's hot, Heather's hot
我们一起来全套...
And we'll go all the way...
我想看她脱光光
I wish I could see her naked
我就为你俯首称臣
And down on all fours.
Ted有个小妹妹
Ted has a little sister
一天比呐一天熟
Gets hotter every day
如我有幸能够见到她
And if I ever meet her
要玩够她的小酥胸! 大家一起来!
With her boobies I will play! Everybody!
妹妹 妹妹 妹妹!
Sister, sister, sister!
干嘛? 光明节我还能接着来
What? I can celebrate Hanukkah, too.
哦 还是他 我看还是接好了
Oh, it's him again. I\nshould probably get it.
嘿 Barney
Hey, Barney.
今晚干嘛?
What's on tap for tonight?
哦 我们打算到Marshall他们家\n看一晚上的Kathy Bates电影 但不看"危情十日"
Oh, we're heading over to Marshall and Lily's\nfor a Kathy Bates movie marathon, but not Misery.
你跟我们一起...
You wanna join us...
他挂了
He hung up.
哦 见到你太好了
Oh, it's great to see you.
嘿 小家伙 你看上去好极了
Hey, kiddo. You look great.
家里一切都好吧?
How are things back home?
嗯 我搬到你以前的房间去了
Well, I moved into your old room.
你知不知道从那能够看到对街\nGottwald太太的卧室呀?
Did you know that you can see strange\nMrs. Gottwald's bedroom across the street?
哦 是啊 我知道
Oh, yes. I am aware of that.
她怎么样?
How's she looking?
Ted 她都62了
Ted, she's 62.
回答问题
Answer the question.
异常精神
Surprisingly perky.
伙计 外面还真冷
Man, it is cold out there.
为啥 你好啊
Why, hello.
我在等你们呢
I've been waiting for you.
等等 那不是我们的椅子
Wait a second. That's not our chair.
你自己搬过来的?
Did you bring that chair yourself?
我想要把会转的
I needed one that swivels.
Heather Mosby...\nHeather Mosby...
Barney Stinson\nBarney. Stinson.
你怎么知道Heather会来?
How did you even know\nHeather was coming into town?
以后再别跟我说事!
Never tell me anything!
你知道我在圣诞前后保守不了秘密的!
You know I can't keep\nsecrets around Christmas!
Robin打算送你个iPod!
Robin's giving you an iPod!
Ted 能到厨房借一步说话么?
Ted, can I chat with you\nfor a sec in the kitchen?
谁都不准碰椅子 是我租的
No one touch the chair. It's a rental.
真不敢相信这么些年来\n你一直把你妹妹藏着不让我见
I can't believe you've been hiding\nyour sister from me all these years.
你怪我?
Do you blame me?
你就像个只会编圣诞歌\n占我妹妹便宜的怪蜀黍
You're like Weird Al Yankovic if he only\nwrote Christmas songs about banging my sister.
好吧 首先 过奖了
Okay. First of all, I'm flattered.
其次 那些只是玩笑而已
Secondly, they're just jokes.
兄弟间开开兄弟妹妹的玩笑而已
A bro can joke about\nanother bro's sister.
又不表明我会付诸行动
It doesn't mean I'm\never gonna act on it.
听着 我爱我妹妹 作为她哥哥
Look, I love my sister,\nand as her older brother,
保护她不被你这种人骗是我的职责
it's my job to protect\nher from guys like you.
你信不过我 是么?
You don't trust me, do you?
是 虽然我也信不过她
No. And I don't trust her either.
那好吧 好极了
Fine. Great.
那我还是拿椅子走人好了
I guess I'll just...\ntake my chair and go.
等等...别...回来...
Wait... Stop... Come back...
Lily跟我打算周日带Heather出去吃晚饭
Lily and I are taking Heather\nout for dinner on Sunday.
你想去吗?
Do you wanna come?
我已经打去餐厅加一个座了
I already called Hurley's\nand added a fourth.
还真不能跟Lily说事
You really can't tell Lily anything.
- 是啊 你不该告诉她的...\n- 老天
- No, you can't tell her...\n- Jeez.
那一年过节 Robin阿姨真的想家了
That year, the holidays were really\nmaking Aunt Robin miss Canada,
所以Marshall就把她带去了\n他想明尼苏达时会去的老地方:
so Marshall brought her to the spot he\nwent whenever he got homesick for Minnesota:
斜眼沙龙
The Walleye Saloon.
晚上好 各位
Evening, everybody.
Marshall!\nMarshall!
这是Robin
Meet Robin.
Robin!\nRobin!
接着喝酒吧
Go back to drinking.
喝!
Drinking!
还好吗 Marshall?
What's up, Marshall?
嘿 你好吗 伙计!
Hey, what's u... Bud!
怎么一瘸一拐的?
What's with the hitch in your giddyap?
哦 我今天玩了会儿曲棍球
Oh, I was playing some hockey today.
膝盖上磨掉了块皮
Tore up something in my knee.
去过医院了吗?
Did you go to the hospital?
没 我就拿啤酒擦了擦
Nah. I just poured some beer on it.
怎么能错过维京队的比赛
Can't miss the Vikes game.
双子城嘞! 噢耶!
Twin Cities! Oh, yeah!
我喜欢这里的伙计们 他们是真爷们
I love the guys here. They're real men.
不弄稀奇古怪的发型 也不美甲
No hair products or manicures.
纽约的男人全部都有些娘娘腔
All New York guys are like 10% girl.
不是吧 这么说可就不公道了
Come on. That seems a little unfair.
我要一份奶油浓汤 只加一勺花蜜
I'll have the vichyssoise with\njust a soupon of cr me fra che.
奶酪之类的吃多了 我容易水肿
Too much dairy and I tend to bloat.
呃...
So...
我今天找到了一套公寓
I found an apartment today.
- 是吗\n- 嗯
- Really?\n- Yeah.
我本来想等你喝高了\n再跟你说这事的 不过...
And I was hoping you'd have a little more\nwine in you before I asked you this, but...
我想让你跟我联名签署租约
I need you to co-sign the lease.
让我想想
Let me think about it.
意思是他不会答应的
That means he's not going to do it.
我真的很需要你帮忙
I could really use your help on this.
我们晚些再谈 好吗
Let's talk about this later, okay?
别妥协
Don't hold your breath.
什么意思? 你信不过我吗?
What is it? You don't trust me?
你是我妹妹
You're my sister.
他只是在陈述事实 不带任何感情色彩
Now he's just stating a fact.
听着 Ted 我很认真地考虑\n在金融界施展一番拳脚 可...
Look, Ted, I am serious about\na career in finance, but...
你却一直把我看做\n想当宇航员的四岁小孩来看
you just keep looking at me like I'm a\nfour-year-old who says she wants to be an astronaut.
我觉得你还没有意识到\n在纽约生存有多难
I just don't think you have any idea\nhow tough it is to make it in New York.
正是 你需要人脉
Exactly. You need connections.
要是Ted认识一个在...
If only Ted knew someone\nwho worked at, say...
比如歌利亚国际银行工作的人 那么...
Goliath National Bank, then...
等等 什么?
wait. What?
我刚好在歌利亚国际银行做事诶
I work at Goliath National Bank.
真是巧哦
How 'bout that?
好了
All right.
两瓶Bemidji生啤 还有...
We got two Bemidji Pale Ales and...
谁点的迷你汉堡?
who ordered the mini-burgers?
偶卖疙瘩! 那是老渔钓鱼么?
Oh, my God! Is that Fisherman's Quest?
我在家的时候老玩那个!
I used to play FQ all\nthe time back home!
哦 是吗? 我的分可高哦
Oh, yeah? I kinda have high score.
不是吹牛 我捉到了...
Not to brag, but I caught...
一条35英寸长的白斑狗鱼
a 35-inch northern pike.
有史以来上钩的最大的鱼
The biggest video fish\nanyone's ever reeled in.
不过是在内河里
I mean... freshwater.
旁门左道的小把戏吧 朋友
A tip of the angler's cap, my friend.
谢谢你带我来这儿
Thank you for bringing me here.
那些是我的
Those are mine.
这样不行
This is not a good idea.
让Heather跟Barney单独在他的办公室?
Heather and Barney alone in his office?
当然我也不想跟她的租约扯上关系
And I certainly don't want to\nbe on the hook for her lease.
她长大了 你不能这么武断
She is growing up. You\njust can't see it yet.
我们说的是一个8个月前\n还因为在商店里偷东西被捕的丫头
We're talking about a girl who was\nbusted for shoplifting eight months ago.
Ted 很多女人都经过\n从商店里偷东西的阶段
Ted, a lot of women go\nthrough a shoplifting phase.
没错 也许今天 \n偶尔她们顺手拿了点便宜货
And sure, maybe to this day, they\nswipe the occasional smaller item
那是因为这种小成就会让她们\n感到性致盎然 都说不清楚为什么的
because it turns them on in a weird\nway that they can't quite explain.
不过...
But...
如果能让你好受些的话\n我明天就跟到歌利亚国际去吧
if it'll make you feel better,\nI-I'll tag along to GNB tomorrow.
我就说要跟Marshall一起吃午饭\n不过实际上 我是监视她跟Barney
I'll say I'm having lunch with Marshall, but\nactually, I'll be spying on her and Barney.
好吧 就那么办吧
Okay. Okay, I'm good with that.
Heather! Heather...
祝你明天在歌利亚国际好运
Heather! Heather... Good\nluck tomorrow at GNB.
我肯定你能让他们死翘翘的
I'm sure you'll knock 'em dead.
我明天会监视你们俩
And I'll be spying on you guys.
见鬼!
Damn it!
我要喝到忘记1999年全美橄榄球\n冠军争夺赛为止?
I'm drinking till I forget\nthe 1999 NFC Championship?
那场比赛
That game.
维京队离超级碗还差2分钟之远了\n可我们的队员
The Vikings were two minutes away from\ngoing to the Super Bowl, when our kicker,
全季比赛一场没落 竟然把球给踢丢了\n使得我们在加时赛里输掉了比赛
who hadn't missed all year shanked a\nfield goal, and we lost in overtime.
妈的!
Damn!
在说99年的冠军争夺赛?
'99 NFC Championship game?
- 是啊\n- 妈的!
- Yeah.\n- Damn!
我爸爸 我一辈子没见过他掉一滴眼泪\n那天却哭了
My dad, who I'd never seen cry\nmy whole life, wiped away a tear.
他说...我心某处已死 儿子
He said... A little part\nof me just died, son.
我喜欢你们对维京队的那股激情
I love how intense you\nguys are about your Vikings.
就好像我在加拿大看曲棍球比赛时...
It's like when we watch\nhockey night in Canada...
干嘛?
What?
别让这里的人知道\n你不是从明尼苏达来的
Don't let anyone in here know\nthat you're not from Minnesota.
为什么? 如果他们知道了会怎么样?
Why? What are they gonna do\nif they find out I'm from...
你觉得这儿像是达拉斯酒吧吗 伙计
Does this look like a\nDallas bar to you, pal?
真奇怪 不过被这样抱着还是蛮舒服的
It's weird, but there's something\ncomforting about being carried like this.
耶!
Yay!
伙计 那家伙简直是
Man, can you believe that guy?
呃...Robin 你从哪儿来的?
So, Robin, where are you from?
Bemidji\nBemidji.
Bemidji 明尼苏达
Bemidji, Minnesota.
维京队 加油!
Go, Vikes!
孩子们 接下来 \n我先说说几天以后的事
Kids, for what happened next, I'm\ngonna jump ahead a couple days.
那公文包真好看
That is a pretty sweet briefcase.
那个摄像头也不错
That's a pretty sweet\nsecurity camera, too.
那边又一个 还有保安呢
And there's another one. And a guard.
我想花钱买的 Ted
I'm planning on paying for it, Ted.
是吗 你还没有找到工作呢
Yeah. Well, you don't have the job yet.
那门是推 不是拉的
That door's a push, not a pull.
对了
There you go.
谢谢你昨天帮忙盯着她
Hey, thanks again for keeping\nan eye on her yesterday.
听着 也许我错了
Look, maybe I was wrong.
听上去她处理同Barney的关系很得体
She sounds like she\nhandled Barney just fine.
也许她能适应纽约的生活
Maybe she'll be able to handle New York.
其实没有谢谢的必要
No thanks necessary!
为什么?
Why not?
我有个秘密 不 我没有!\n什么事都没发生 发生了点事!
I have a secret. No, I don't!\nNothing happened. Something happened.
出了什么事?
What happened?
没什么 在Heather面试之后
Nothing.After Heather's interview,
我跑去和Marshall打了下招呼 \n然后等我回去...
I went to say hi to Marshall for a\nfew minutes, and when I came back...
天啊
Oh, my God!
Lily Lily 在你说什么或做什么之前 \n我想求你件事
Lily, Lily, before you say or\ndo anything, I beg you one favor.
什么?
What?
别踩了 那可是Prada的
Get off that. It's Prada.
我真的很抱歉
I am so sorry.
我早就知道 从开始就知道
I knew it. I knew it all along.
她还是过去那个不负责任的家伙 \n等我见到Barney...
She is still the same, irresponsible train wreck\nthat she always was, and when I see Barney...
你什么也不会说
You won't say a word.
Ted Heather求我不要告诉你
Ted, Heather begged me not to tell you.
如果知道我乱说 肯定会恨我入骨
She will hate my guts if\nshe knows that I blabbed.
我真喜欢那个包包 但我买不起
Oh, I love that briefcase,\nbut I can't afford it.
你是对的 Ted
You were right, Ted.
我一直是对的
I certainly was.
瞧见了没 她没有拿那个包包 \n这就是负责任的表现
See? She didn't get the\nbriefcase! That's responsible!
而且她也没有和里面任何人胡搞
And there's almost no way she\nhad sex with anyone in there.
改过自新了吧
Turning over a new leaf.
晚上好 各位!
Evening, everybody!
所以我爸爸和我去了\n99年NFC冠军杯现场
So my dad and I are at the\n'99 NFC Championship game.
我说晚上好 各位!
I say evening, everybody!
当我们错过了触底得分的机会 \n而输掉比赛...
And when we missed that\nfield goal and lost...
- 妈的!\n- 妈的! 妈的
- Damn!\n- Damn! Damn.
我爸爸 这辈子我从未见过他流泪
my dad, who I had never\nseen cry in my entire life,
擦去一滴眼泪 然后说
wiped away a tear and said,
我心某处已死 儿子
A little part of me just died, son.
儿子?
Son?
我准备这样告诉我的儿子
I told it the way I'm gonna tell my son.
如果我够幸运能有个儿子 然后取名为
If I'm ever lucky enough\nto have a son, and name him
Rashad Tarkenton\nRashad Tarkenton.
Robin 故事真赞 故事真赞!
Robin, great story. Great story!
但听起来有点耳熟
But it does sound a little bit familiar.
我知道!
I know!
他们居然完全相信
They totally ate it up.
我知道你来这里干嘛了
I see what you're doing here.
什么?
What?
我带你来是好意...
I brought you here as a favor because...
因为我对你感到抱歉 明白吗
because I felt sorry for you, okay?
现在你却想偷走我的酒吧
And now it's like you're\ntrying to steal my bar.
你觉得我想偷走你的酒吧?
You think I'm trying to steal your bar?
少来了你
Oh, get oot.
少来了? 怎么 你是加拿大人吗
Get oot? What, are you Canadian?
不 我...
No, I...
如果你想模仿加拿大人 \n只要关掉灯大声喊就行了!
You want to impersonate a Canadian, just\nturn of the lights and get all scared!
什么意思?
What was that?
对边境那边的加拿大人
Oh, well, with Canada\nright across the border,
我们明尼苏达州人有时候喜欢嘲笑他们
we Minnesotans sometimes like to\nmake jokes at your guys' expense
而且差不多是同样的主题
and they're all sort\nof along the same theme.
说我们怕黑吗?
That we're afraid of the dark?
对
Yeah.
比如说 嘿 大家 换个灯泡\n需要多少个加拿大人呢
For example: Uh, hey, everyone, how many\nCanadians does it take to change a lightbulb?
啥? 哦不 灯泡不亮了? 我好怕~
What? Oh, no, the\nlightbulb's out? I'm scared!
这也太白痴了
That is insane.
你凭什么认为我们加拿大人就怕黑呢
Why do you think the Canadians\nare afraid of the dark?
一切偏见从何而来 Robin?
Well, where does any\nprejudice come from, Robin?
一旦古板老套形成 \n忽然间就一传十 十传百
A stereotype starts, and all of\na sudden it spreads like wildfire.
比如亚洲人不会开车 苏格兰人卑鄙 \n巴西人邮票总是贴的过多
Like Asians can't drive, Scotsmen are cheap,\nBrazilians always put on way too much postage.
我想这个问题是没法解决的 Robin
I just don't think this\nis gonna work out, Robin.
你不能和那些轻视你伟大祖国的人\n一起玩 来 我送你出去
You can't be hanging out with people who belittle\nyour beloved homeland, so I'll walk you out.
不 等下 我还有话说
No, wait, I have something to say.
嘿 各位
Hey, everybody.
让我告诉你们一些关于加拿大的事
Let me tell you something\nabout people from Canada.
嘿 Robin 别闹笑话了
Hey, Robin, please don't make a scene.
你们知道为什么加拿大人\n过生日从来都不许愿的吗
Do you know why Canadians\nnever get a birthday wish?
因为他们怕吹熄蜡烛
Because they're too afraid\nto blow out the candles.
天啊 我真喜欢这里
Oh, God, I love it here. God.
我想你在歌利亚国家银行\n前途一片光明
I think your prospects at GNB are good.
你明确的表明你愿意去任何职位\n(愿意采用任何体位)
You certainly made it clear\nyou're will to take any position.
这是新的杯垫吗?
Are these new coasters?
我希望你能得到这份工作
Well, I hope you get the job.
我最爱的就是填补空职位了\n(我最爱OOXX了)
Nothing gives me more pleasure\nthan filling an opening.
我发誓这杯垫比原来的厚了
I swear to God these\ncoasters are thicker.
我愿意尽自己最大的力量\n(我愿意弯下腰从后面...)
Well, I am willing to\nbend over backwards.
好了 够了!
Okay, that's it!
真不敢相信你上了我妹妹
I cannot believe you\nhad sex with my sister!
你居然泄密!
You blabbed?
知道吗 这还是旧杯垫
Do you know what? This is a\nnew batch of the old coasters.
我去找酒保确认下
I'm just gonna confirm\nthat with the bartender.
还有你 你觉得自己现在成熟了 \n能负责任了?
And you, you're mature\nand responsible now?
你来到纽约应征的第一份工作
Is it mature and responsible to go to your\nfirst big job interview in New York City
就上了个陌生人 这样做是成熟 \n负责任的表现吗
and nail a total stranger?
你一直以来都是不成熟 不负责任的
You've always been\nimmature and irresponsible.
而且你也会继续不成熟 不负责任下去
You will always be\nimmature and irresponsible.
我连图书馆借阅证都不会签 \n就更别提租约了
And I wouldn't cosign a library\ncard for you, let alone a lease.
Barney和我没有上床
Barney and I didn't have sex.
省省吧 Lily都看到了
Save it. Lily saw you.
或者说 她真的看到了吗?
Or did she?
听着 Ted 你对Heather和我太没有信心...
You see, Ted, you had so little\nfaith in Heather and me...
因此我们决定呈现给你想要的一切
we decided to give you exactly\nwhat you expected of us.
而且我知道凭着Lily的一张嘴\n就会宣扬出去
And I knew we could\ncount on Lily to blab.
天啊
Oh, my God!
什么? 你们为什么要那么做?
What? Why would you do that?
因为你活该
Because you deserved it.
Ted 你知道我不是圣人
Ted, you know I'm no saint.
是的 我开车送你妈妈\n去机场的时候的确...
And yes, it's true that time I\ndrove your mother to the airport,
我们暂且称其为混乱
well, let's just say\nthere was a very confusing,
又充满性诱惑的短短的停车时刻
sexually charged moment\nin short-term parking,
但我说过不会碰你妹妹 我是认真的
but I said I would never go\nnear your sister, and I meant it.
你应该相信我
You should have trusted me.
你如此坚信我还是那个无法无天的\n小女孩 缺忽略了我长大了的事实
You're so convinced I'm still some out-of-control\nteenager, you missed the fact I grew up.
我去住酒店
I'm gonna find a hotel.
晚点回去收拾东西
I'll get my things later.
圣诞快乐
Merry Christmas.
你妈妈和我打啵了
Your mom and I kissed.
最好快点 你还有五秒钟时间钓两条鲟鱼
Better get a move on. You got five\nseconds to catch two more sturgeon.
嘿 抓鱼大场面
Hey, we got a possible gill screen.
得了 你不可能用一个钩钓两条鱼的
Forget it. You can't catch\ntwo fish with one hook.
对 但我可以先钓上一条
No, but I can catch one fish
然后用它再做饵去钓另一条
and use that fish to\ncatch the other one.
最高分! 你击败了Marshall!
High score! You beat Marshall!
她是加拿大人!\n（发飙了!）
She's Canadian!
Robin是加拿大人!
Robin's Canadian!
她是加拿大人
She's Canadian.
她不是从Bemidji来的 \n而且对维京队一无所知
She's not from Bemidji and she doesn't\nknow a darn thing about the Vikings.
你只是气她得了最高分
You're just mad 'cause\nshe got high score.
Robin 在99年NFC冠军杯比赛上 \n当维京队输了比赛...
Robin, in the '99 NFC Championship\ngame when the Vikings lost...
- 妈的!\n- 哦 妈的!
- Damn!\n- Oh, damn!
错失触底得分机会的是谁?
who was the kicker who\nmissed the field goal?
Rashad Tarkenton\nRashad Tarkenton.
是Gary Anderson
Gary Anderson.
他现在退役了
He's now retired.
在加拿大开了飞钓的买卖
Owns a fly-fishing\nbusiness... in Canada.
再见 Robin
Good-bye, Robin.
不 你们知道吗
No. You know what?
很高兴你们发现我说"少来" \n因为我很高兴是加拿大人
I'm glad you found oot because\nI'm proud to be Canadian.
我们也许没有梦幻橄榄球队 也没有Prince
We may not have a fancy\nNFL team or Prince,
但我们发明了棋盘游戏
but we invented Trivial Pursuit.
不客气 地球人!
You're welcome, Earth!
另外在加拿大 你可以去全裸\n脱衣舞俱乐部 还可以要酒喝
Plus in Canada, you can go to an\nall-nude strip club and order alcohol.
没错
That's right.
从Moosejaw到Fundy湾 \n你可以喝20盎司比尔森啤酒
From Moosejaw to the Bay of Fundy,\nyou can suck down a 20-ounce pilsner
还可以欣赏某个煤矿工人女儿的\n脱衣舞表演
while watching some coal miner's\ndaughter strip down to her pelt.
嫉妒了吧?
Jealous?
在加拿大 人们不在意你从哪里来 \n只要你很友善
In Canada people don't care where\nyou're from, as long as you're friendly
或者借他们一根烟 递个甜甜圈之类的
and maybe loan them a\nsmoke or hand over a donut.
我很骄傲自己从白色的北国而来...
I'm proud to be from\nthe Great White North...
我希望现在就能在那里
and I wish I was there right now.
还有 我们不怕黑
And we're not afraid of the dark.
我们是不喜欢 但又有谁喜欢黑呢
I mean, we don't love it, but who does?
圣诞快乐
Merry Christmas.
- Ted...
- 看看里面
- Ted...\n- Look inside.
如果你往中间按...
You just, if you push it towards the...
不是往下 往中间
Not down, towards the middle.
- 不用你帮忙\n- 好吧
- Don't need your help.\n- Got it.
你签了租约
You signed the lease.
是的 知道原因吗
Yeah. You know why?
因为你相信我 认为这是个好主意吗
Because you trust me and\nthink it's a great idea?
因为我想要了解你
Because I want to get to know you.
了解这个全新的你
The new you.
谢谢
Thanks.
再说一句 搬了新地方
By the way, in your new neighborhood,
你真的得弄一个结实的锁
you really should get a good\nsolid deadbolt for the door.
如果你想...活命的话
If you want... to live.
很抱歉刚才的事
I'm so sorry for what\nhappened back there.
我简直像十足的混蛋
I-I acted like a total jerk.
我 我不该说那些
I, I shouldn't have said anything.
不 听着 我很抱歉
No, look, I'm sorry.
那里是你的地方
That was your place.
我不该想把它变成我的地方
I shouldn't have tried to make it mine.
只是每年这个时候 我都很想家
Just every year at the\nholidays, I get homesick.
至今为止 每年我都有理由留下: \n男友 工作 或者别的什么
And so far, every year I've had a reason\nto stay: a boyfriend, a job, or something.
但今年是第一次 我找不到理由
But this year for the\nfirst time, I don't.
不 你有的
Yes, you do.
是什么?
What?
因为我们都爱你
We all love you, okay?
如果你搬回加拿大 \n我们会跳上飞机 抓到你
If you ever moved back to Canada, we would\nhop on a plane, we would track you down,
在Barney拉着我们去参观你说的\n那些脱衣舞俱乐部之后
and after Barney dragged us to a few\nof those strip clubs you talked about,
我们会把你带回来这里 \n你本该在的地方
we would bring you back right\nhere where you're supposed to be.
没有...
It's...
没有Robin Scherbatsky \n这里就不是纽约了
it's not New York\nwithout Robin Scherbatsky.
- 谢谢\n- 没事
- Thanks.\n- Yeah.
只是有时候我真的想家
I just miss it there sometimes.
我真希望能眨眨眼回去一个小时
I wish I could blink my eyes and be\nback in Canada for an hour, you know?
我还真希望你这么说
I was hoping you would say that.
* Once, there was this girl *\n* Once, there was this girl *
* Who wouldn't go and change *\n* Who wouldn't go and change *
* With the girls in the change room...*\n* With the girls in the change room...*
觉得这地方咋样
How did you find this place?
像回到家了 对吗
Feels like home, right?
有个办法可以证明
There's one way to find out.
不好意思 没看到你 你还好吗
Well, sorry there. Didn't\nsee ya. Are you okay?
我没事
I'm fine.
好吧 万分抱歉
Okay, sorry aboot that.
来个甜甜圈吧 免费的
Have a donut on the hoose.
- 谢谢\n- 不用谢
- Thanks.\n- Okay.
好吧 你撞到他 他反而向你道歉 \n还请你免费吃甜甜圈?
Okay, you bumped into him, and he\napologized and gave you a donut on the hoose?
真是家的感觉啊
Oh, it's just like home.
抱歉! 没事没事! 抱歉
Sorry! It's gonna be fine! Sorry.
没有人喜欢黑暗
No one likes the dark.
下面登场的是来自安大略的
Marshall Erickson\nNext up from Ontario: Marshall Erickson.
都不知道你要上去呢 准备唱什么?
I didn't know you signed\nup. What are you gonna sing?
我想你会听出来的
Oh, I think you'll recognize it.
* But that's okay, I'm\ngonna rock your body anyway *
(Robin做青少年偶像唱的歌 hihaha)
* I'm gonna rock your\nbody to Canada Day!*\n* I'm gonna rock your\nbody to Canada Day!*
* Buddy, you can turn off the\nscreen. We know the lyrics.*\n* Buddy, you can turn off the\nscreen. We know the lyrics.*
* Everybody come and play *\n* Everybody come and play *
* Throw every last care away *\n* Throw every last care away *
* Let's go to the mall today!*\n* Let's go to the mall today!*